here in the team auditorium with the man
AP Adam Peters in the building. Sir,
thank you so much for taking the time.
>> Thank you.
>> What an off seasonason it has been for
you.
>> Yeah,
>> it's going. You have everybody buzzing
right now because of these new jerseys,
showing love to the past, but also being
excited about the future. How excited
are you for the reaction to the new
jerseys?
>> Yeah, first of all, I wish I could take
credit, you know, but that was the the
vision of our ownership group. um and
Josh and then uh our our business side
making it come to life, you know, Mark
Klaus and Patrick Arthur and everybody
and just like everybody, social media
team, marketing, just like showing like
how cool uh you know, dipping into our
past is and and I'm pretty juiced about
it, dude. I I can't lie. Um I was really
pumped when we had him last year for the
throwbacks and then having those be our
permanent uh uniforms just feels right.
Well, something you can't take a little
bit of credit for at least is this free
agency pool that we just had. I mean,
Dan Orlovski spoke to me a few weeks ago
and said he feels the Commanders won
free agency, and I know that has to be
something that you really really are
excited about. How do you feel about all
of these new guys that we brought in?
>> Um, I want I want to win the games, not
free agency, right? But um but that
being said, uh really excited about the
guys, not not just the players, but the
people that we brought in, the guys that
we brought back from our own team. Uh
that was really important. And then
going out and getting some guys, some
speed, some youth and and some real
energy in the building. And it was
really fun when they all came in, we
signed them and and got to welcome them
and you could just feel the the energy
back in the building. It was it was
really cool. So, um, they're coming in
on Monday, uh, for, uh, the offseason
program, and I can't wait.
>> I appreciate the humility, man, but it's
been dope watching you cook in free
agency these last years. It's funny, we
were talking before we started
recording, and this has been a tradition
for us. This is our third year sitting
here before the draft. And I don't know
if you remember, but last year when we
sat here, I asked you about free agency,
and you said if we had to play a game
today, this was before the draft, you
said we would be ready to play the
draft. It's just a bonus. Do you feel
that way about this free point where the
ste team stands today?
>> Yeah, I do. I think we all do. And um
that's the goal. I think you never want
to have glaring holes where you feel
like you got to go reach for somebody um
and not picking the best player
available that can help your team. So,
uh we feel we put ourselves in that
position and and that's our mindset
going into the draft.
>> And you talk about the draft and there's
a lot of talent in this draft all
through it. But when you look at just
the pool as a whole, this talent that's
in the draft this year, what does it
make you feel like is one of the best
prospect evaluators in the game?
>> Um, you know, I I think I'd start with,
you know, where we're sitting at pick
seven. And I feel really good about, you
know, getting a really good player
there. So, I think that's that's the the
first first part of it. And there's so
many good players at so many different
spots. You know, you could really fill
in the whole team and see there's going
to be a good player at any position,
which is cool. So we can just go ahead
and pick who we think is best. But you
can always find the gyms late in the
draft and and that's where our our
college scouts, you know, they make
their hey on day three. And they've done
a great job these last couple years of
really um setting the table and really
letting us know who they really like.
You know, not just, you know, on the
tape, but what what makes these guys
tick, you know, the type of people they
are, the the human beings, how much they
love football, teammate, and all the
different things that make you a great
pro. So that process, although you get
more attention on the first round pick,
that that part's my favorite.
>> Oh man, I could tell how much you love
the scouting process and you guys made a
little bit of headlines when you said,
"Hey, we're going to go all hands on
deck to Ohio State Pro Day. We know how
many prospects are over there at Ohio
State." What made you decide to say,
"Hey, we all need to be present for this
one."
>> Yeah. Well, we were sitting in the draft
room for about a week and it's starting
to get dingy and dark, so we need to get
out. I know. Um it was uh it just made
sense. Honestly, it made sense where um
we it's it's a quick flight. It's about
an hour flight and um they really have
10 guys or sorry, four guys that can go
in the top 10 and then another few other
really good prospects as well. So, and
on both sides of the ball. So, um it and
we had some time. We always build in
some time in our draft process for
contingencies and whatnot and and we
just said this would be really good to
go there, see these guys, always get
another touch point on them. you know,
that's always good. As many touch
points, I think, as you can get to
understand, you know, make, you know,
get comfortable with a person. Um, they
have a great coaching staff there that
we're able to to tap into when we're out
there and talk to coach Patricia, uh,
the best defensive coordinator in in
college football. And, uh, he gave us
great insight into his defensive guys.
Coach Coach Day gave us great insight in
the offensive guys. And so, it was
definitely worthwhile.
>> And there's so many things goes into
this offseason, right? It's not just the
draft stuff. It's not just the free
agency. It's also coaching staff,
personnel and things of that nature. For
the first time, UN and DQ got to go get
two new coordinators together, one
offensive coordinator, one defensive
coordinator, Donte Jones, David Blau,
what goes into that decision- making to
bring two up and cominging stars in the
game here as our coordinators?
>> Well, I think, you know, I think really
hats off to DQ. you know, he led that
process and and he did he was extremely
thorough in terms of, you know, combing
the league, combing every, you know,
everywhere to find, you know, the
different candidates of all kinds of
different, you know, expertise and
background and all that. I think he did
a great job identifying two guys that
have been so far just fantastic and and
I have no doubt they they'll continue to
be that once we get the guys in and and
start installing everything. But in
terms of where I'm at, you know, the
processes that we've been through so
far, free agency, they've both been
awesome. And then the draft, they've
both been awesome and and they're great
guys to work with and just great guys to
be around. So, um, that all helps and
and I know they're going to be really
good on the grass. And
>> for the third season, UNDQ get to be in
the draft room. Now, it's a new draft
room this time, which I know you're
excited about, but that process about
collaborating, we talk about it every
year, you and him being able to
collaborate on these prospects. What's
your favorite part about being in that
draft room with DQ?
>> Yeah, I think I mean one just you know
sitting sitting next to them being able
to to discuss things but then just you
know we see same things the same way you
know in terms of just football players
and and what we're looking for and so
you know we can kind of see all right
that's a commander right there you know
and you kind of you feel that and then
you know draft day um that's always fun.
There's a lot of dead times. You can
joke around a little bit, but uh when it
comes time to to get ready and make the
picks, you know, we do a great job of
talking through it. You know, you know,
listening to everybody's opinion and but
ultimately it's it's us and um you know,
we we've been really good at working
together.
>> We're so excited again to see you and DQ
there together in that draft room. AP,
we can't wait. Thank you for taking the
time. You know, the kids are saying,
"Let AP cook." And that's exactly what
we want to see. AP cook. AP, we
appreciate you so much, sir.
>> Appreciate it, man.
>> Yes, sir. hike you with.